756 West Peachtree Street, CODA E0951 Atlanta, GA 30332 U.S.A.

ChangSeok Oh

Profile: https://shivamidow.github.io E-mail: changseok@gnome.org Mobile: +1 (404) 740-7896

Open source enthusiast and hacker specializing in web technology and linux-based systems. A WebKit and GNOME project contributor. More than 8 years experience at major players in the industry. Looking for opportunities in Web browser, Web Security & Privacy, Browser Security, Kernel, and Computer Graphics.

Skills

WebKit, Blink/Chromium, GNOME, Linux, C/C++, Python, HTML/CSS/Javascript, Objective-C, Java, OpenGL/OpenGL ES, Clutter, Computer Graphics, GTK+, eBPF, BCC, Ethereum, Git, OBS, Clang, LLVM, GStreamer, Tizen, Linux Perf, Bluetooth LE, ReactJS, React Native, Embedded system, Puppeteer

Education

08/2017 - present
08/2017 - 08/2019
08/2017 - 08/2019
03/2000 - 06/2008

Ph.D student in Computer Science, Georgia Tech in Atlanta, GA, U.S.A.
Advisor: Prof. Wenke Lee, Co-Advisor: Prof. Paul Pearce
M.S. in Computer Science (Computer Systems, GPA: 3.87 / 4.0), Georgia Tech in Atlanta, GA, U.S.A.
Dual B.E. in Digital Media and Computer Engineering, Ajou University, South Korea

Professional Experience

_				
06/2019 - present	Intern at Igalia, S.L. in A Coruña, Spain			
	Bring ANGLE backend for WebGL to WebKitGTK			
	• Zero copy texture sharing between Mesa and ANGLE via Linux DMA buffer			
	• Implement various Web Standards (e.g., AVIF, Gamepad, Form Validation and Web Speech) in WebKit			
05/2020 - 08/2020	Intern at Samsung Research America in Mountain View, CA			
05/2019 - 08/2019	Build a web app for health data analysis with ReactJS (frontend) and Node.js (backend)			
	Built an automated system that verifies UI of a watch app by using Tizen automation framework			
	Profiled memory usage and revealed possible memory leak of a watch app by using Valgrind			
	• Implemented file transfer via Bluetooth LE in an React Native watch application			
08/2012 - 03/2016	Software engineer at Collabora Ltd. in Cambridge, UK			
	Developed hardware based compositing based on Clutter in WebKit			
	• Resource efficient web browser based on GNOME Epiphany for Raspberry Pi 2+			
	Customized WebKit features and API set for Smart TV Alliance SDK			
07/2008 - 08/2012	Assistant Software engineer at Samsung Electronics in Suwon, South Korea			
	• Developed an in-house web layout engine for Smart TVs, Printers in C++			
	• Implemented WebGL and Accelerated Compositing in WebKit EFL by using OpenGL ES for Tizen			
07/2007 - 06/2008	Intern at Samsung Software Membership in Suwon, South Korea			
	Developed a 3D racing game using DirectX on Windows (video)			

Academic Experience

05/2021 - 08/2021	Research Intern at Tandon School of Engineering, New York University			
	Research a web privacy issue with Prof. Damon McCoy			
08/2019 - 05/2021	Teaching Assistant at School of Computer Science, Georgia Tech			
	• CS 6262: Network Security, Design and Implement the XSS task using node.js and Chrome Extension			
	CS 6035: Intro to Info Sec			
08/2017 - present	resent Research Assistant at School of Computer Science, Georgia Tech			
	Redesign chromium to block user tracking with web browser fingerprints			
	• Debloat chrome browser with feature sunsetting on the fly by binary rewriting			
	• Developed a defense system against micro DDoS by profiling resources with HPC (Intel PCM, MBM)			
	• Implemented an idle profiler that diagnoses off-cpu time in multi-threaded program using HPC			

Open Source Projects

Open Source Projects				
04/2013 - present	Committer at WebKit (patches)			
	• Implement Web Speech (Text-to-Speech)			
	• Implement Gamepad API with libmanette			
	• Implement AVIF image decoder with dav1d			
	• Implemented OpenGL ES backend for Accelerated Compositing.			
	 Developed memory pressure handler that copes with out-of-memory on top of Linux cgroup. 			
	Enhance WebGL support and Fix layout and rendering issues			
	• Fix CVE security bugs in WebKit (CVE-2020-10018, CVE-2020-11793)			
10/2013 - present	Member at GNOME foundation (patches)			
	Translate GNOME Web and its Help document in Korean			
01/2015 - present	Contributor at Chromium/Blink (patches)			
	• Implemented a CSS spec called font-size-adjust			
	Fix layout and rendering issues in blink			

Publication

CCS 2020	Slimium: Debloating the Chromium Browser with Feature Subsettin	g (paper)
Patents		
US 20110296323 US 20110289110 US 20110093606 US 20110090165	Web page management method and apparatus and storage medium thereof Method of re-searching webpage and apparatus and storage medium therefor Interface method and display device Interface method and display device	
Presentations		
12/07/2014 09/29/2014 04/25/2014 10/27/2013	Web Engines Hackfest 2014 in A Coruña, Spain (slides) DEVIEW 2014 in Seoul, South Korea (slides, video) Jeju University in Jeju, South Korea (slides) DevOn 2013 in Seoul, South Korea (slides)	
		Last undata : 06/02/2021

Last update : 06/02/2021